And we have installed golden lights in this house
because golden lights give a
warm look.  Sounds like a good one.
This is extra parts.  All this will
go inside it.  Everything like kalaja etc will go inside.
Ok?  This is a keep egg.  Everything will
go.
This tea always falls down.  Stop.   stop stop.
What is he doing?  Electrical work.
Pulling the main electric cable.
How is he pulling it?
Oh I
came,
mom had given me one a while ago, it is very
sweet, wow, look, Mashallah Mashallah, my
own plants,
yes, yes, it is on top too, do you give paper, ok,
eat pakki, they
eat pakki, that's why mom has
tied it and covered it, otherwise
birds eat it,
mom, peel many flowers,
200, you are cute,
200, there were many guavas inside it, meaning so many
plants,
yes, with this many
Aryan is playing right now, it is fun in the mud,
Aryan, it is fun, this is what
he wanted, he was waiting since long,
Bishal will go, I will play in the mud,
Aryan, eat this and go quickly, who will come to
mom, who will come fast, run
Aryan,
mom will come only.  Yes
mom, mom,
mom will come.
Make gutta make gutta gutta
make gutta.  You make it, make it with a spoon.
Mom,
Aryan has found his new friend.
Aryan is your new friend.  Mustaqeem
dog, drink it.
Oh, build a house.  Make it with Mustaqeem.  You
sandals po sandals why don't you open them
yes
Mustaqeem is eating guava Aryan also
ate guava just now now give both and claim
see keep my [ __ ]
pit Aryan has made a pit see guys
Mustaqeem's bungalow is a bit different
I don't understand what he is saying when
I talk to him or ask him anything
he replies but I do
n't understand anything he says.  Hit the peepada, you
eat the peepada and hit the peepada.
I am asking the ant.  Do you
kill ants?  Ants say Peepra.  Bengali
Pipra This is Pipra.
Aryan
Aryan you got stuck.
Look at the children's play styles.
Look at the play, I will see something with my nails
Aryan, you will make a heart for mom with your nails,
make it with a spoon, what are you
making Aryan, what are you drawing,
I am driving the car,
you are driving the car,
oy oy Mustaqeem, is there a pothole in the car,
how did Mustaqeem take the car into the pothole,
Aryan, you will see, you want to see, you want to
play together, it is
so nice, the sounds of the birds are
coming.
I am back in my comfortable
clothes
and right now we are sitting after having breakfast.
Spoon Here Your Spoon This One is looking for a spoon.
Look who hid the spoon, you yourself hid it
and then you yourself are searching for the spoon.
Finally, after waiting for three-four hours, I got
this cable worth Rs 10.
Now I am going back to the same place
where I had parked my boat.
But here the
weather has become very bad because
storms can come anytime.  It became dark and the entire
sky was filled with clouds.  So it would be
better for me to cross the river quickly.
So we passed by that place
and while going, we placed this wire in the middle so that it does
not fall.  And this person in the boat was actually
fishing.  He
caught only one fish the whole day.
This is Palla, child, Palla.  Meaning, it is so small that he cannot even eat it.
So the sky became completely dark
and the waves were also very high
this time because it would start raining soon
and the waves were
coming inside the boat.  Due to the jolt with the boat,
our pants and shoes got wet.  So it was
very dangerous.  It was a bit dangerous on the return journey
because even Abba got
tensed waiting for me.  That father was waiting for me on the bank asking
where we were and
why we had not crossed the river yet.  It
started raining heavily.  On top of that the waves were also
very high.  Due to which everyone in the house was
tense.  Maybe for the first time there was a
shore nearby, then I was
searching everywhere to see if there was any place nearby where I could catch hold of it
if I drowned.  This tension was always there.   There is a
time to go and there is a time to come back.
Check out this view from Mashallah.  This father and
son are both sleeping on the sofa.
Aryan normally does not sleep during the day
but suddenly he has fallen asleep.  And let
me show you a nice view.  Hey, are
you up?   You were
not acting, I had to get a
lot of work done from you, come let me
show you one thing, you were sleeping, right, there is
a bird outside, it is
raining, let me
show you, it is raining here, here
I will go and see the birds, oh, they are eating even in the rain,
how many, right now I can
see two, they flew away,
50-60 come at a good time,
mother said, she gives it in the morning at the time of Fajr, then
this entire ground gets filled.   There will be a
video of that time.
Hey look, water is coming in when the window is opened.
Why?   He will
come soon.  It is raining heavily right now
brother
and it is fun.  Hey, his sleep got disturbed.
Friends, you must remember that
we had bought these switches when Iman and I had gone there.   Is
n't it Eman?  We were
two years and a half ago.   I think
two years ago.  So it took a
lot of time for the poor guy to do this.  And all this is the
hard work of the mother which she has done after looking at each and every thing.
And these ones look very nice
in this house.  The grey colour means theme so there are
lots of grey grey switches
and yellow lights.  So look,
even without lights you get a nice cool view.  There
is no need for AC here, friend.
I had put sheets and blankets on my sister's bed and I
know I had even turned off the fan at night.  It
was so cold at night.   Was
dying.
So right now it is the rainy season.  So now
I will make some delicious hot tea for us.
Then we eat and we have
installed golden lights in this house because golden
lights give a warm look and
look nice and when I had not come to this house, at least it looks
different, the white light in Dhaka,
here also there is white light of white colour, here
also it will feel that I am in the same place, same
environment, that is why
different lights were provided, brother it is different or at other
places,
yes it was Imon's idea that whatever lights we provide for so
many buildings, all of them are over
and this is another reason of his too, you have made it white, do you
know why?
Why?
Because when you asked Chat GBD,
put white lights in this house.
I had asked Chatji to take photos from outside and then
I had asked him to light this building properly.
Then what did Chat GBT do
?  Yellow light gave warm light.
I felt so much better after that.  Then
after that, the world
means if you look outside the building at night,
if all the lights are on in the house, then
my JGBT is completely with me, that is,
JB is completely with me, that is my boyfriend.
Yes, stop it now.  I have spoken enough.
Assalamu Alaikum and hey friends welcome back
to my channel.  So early in the morning we are
making breakfast in Bighal.  I have made these rotis.
All the poor parathas got burnt a little.  They have been
broken and taken out like this.  All these kebabs are ready.
Our tea is being made here.
This is our sausage.  So here is our
view of the kitchen.  There is a nice
breeze coming from here from outside.  So this is
our kitchen and
here is mother's stuff.  Spices
etc. are here.  This stuff is there.
Here is the stuff.  So this is our nice and
lovely kitchen.  Where this is
becoming our breakfast, our first breakfast.  So
Mashaallah Mashaallah, I am having fun
in the village, friend.  What an atmosphere it is.  So
they remove all the garbage from the paratha packets
and quickly have their breakfast
ready.  By the way, there is no gas here.
So look, this is the cylinder, this one
is running and it scares me a lot.
Yes Abba
Internet yes yes ok yes yes yes
this tea always falls.
Stop stop stop I will turn it on again.
Because this tea keeps falling from my hands.  I had
made it once before.  She had fallen.
You
Ashish Sona ji,
tea is ready, paratha is ready, come on, he is doing
this electrical work, he is
pulling the electric cable,
how is he pulling it, the
purpose is with water,
put the wire,
today I am going to make roasted duck, roasted duck, for that
I need all these things, so come on, let me
quickly grind some things
and some onions, we do
tadka like this, not tadka, we will do the
sautéing in the beginning, so
first of all, I will
chop some garlic, ginger ginger in small pieces.  So, since these are very big, it will take a
lot of time to grind them.  The
knife is very sharp.  So you will have to do it carefully.
So these ones will all keep grinding.
This is also there.  I do
n't need so many of them.  Adding too much ginger will make it
too bitter.  I think this is enough.
And after that the garlic will go away as it is.
I will fry some onions.
So let's chop some onions.
Every knife is different.
So this knife is a little difficult to hold.   There
is also a big knife.  I can use that too.
But we manage with this only.  Let us go.
Abba had brought fresh duck even
before we came, that duck was growing
on our terrace till we
came, then yesterday its father said
Allahu Akbar to it and forced it to cook, and today
I am going to make its roasted duck,
freshly cooked, so let's cook it quickly, I
will fry some onion, rest all this,
why have you put grind right, I
question each and every thing for you.   There is a
yellow light in your room, isn't there a yellow
light?  This duck masala is ready.   Did
not add chillies.  Children will eat it
and this one is a duck.  Its feet also go
inside it.  Ok?  Everything is clean.
Mother has kept everything clean.  This
is duck meat.  So this one is my own duck.
This is his nirgat.  A big drain.  It
was a very big duck.  I might have made a video or
not, I don't know, if I will watch the video, then
this is its meat and its extra parts,
everything will go inside it, liver etc.
everything will go inside, okay, keep this egg aside,
everything will go inside, so right now it is just a little
fried, I will put it in now and Eamon is
going to bathe Aryan because there is
a fun here for Aryan, he
plays in the mud again and again, as soon as Aryan
comes out of the house, he goes to the mud
ground, then what he does is that he keeps playing.
The vehicles take the gardens.
He also has a friend here and
keeps playing with him.  Then Aryan will take a bath and
then have breakfast.  I woke up early in the morning and
went out.  So this is an
interesting thing that happens in the village that the children get
very much in tune with the nature.  Let's play.
So let's
cut fresh guavas from our own trees right now.  Come on,
how
healthy will it be with Mashallah.  No chemicals whatsoever.  The plants that
we buy from the market or grow by giving them chemical preparations are
chemical free.  Its peels are also eaten.
So now peel it or
eat it like this.
All the peels are there.
Will you eat?   There are no
pesticides, nothing.  It has come from Just Pay.
Yes.  Now whatever
we eat from the market, because
whatever is given in the market, they
give chemicals to preserve it. They
give chemicals so that it gets cooked.  When a child is born, he
gives chemicals.  When he becomes old, he gives chemicals.
Yes.  Let's cut it as it is now.  Ok?
let's Eat.  Fresh fruit.  Whenever we
eat even one thing from our own village, from the
trees, mother and father become so happy.  If we are
so happy then
we will quickly eat every tree that is there.  I'll also give you a tour of
all our plants.
And three,
mom, it is
very tasty, so
our roasted duck is
ready, and here in Bangladesh,
rice roti with duck is famous,
so this mom has made a type of roti, it is
called Siddha roti, this is also very
tasty, it is a complicated
process.  It is not easy to make and
it is very tasty to eat.
So I also enjoy Bangladeshi food a
lot.  And when I feel like eating
Pakistani food, I
also enjoy Pakistani food.  So till now
we enjoy our village life.
See you in my next vlog.  God
bless you.  Bye-B
[Music]
Tu Awash
Koni Sin
[Music]
Go